不公平！这是我的钱
It's not fair! It's my money,
我知道，但这是布莱的心愿
I know, But it's what Brad wanted,
-这人是谁？ -她是布莱的遗孀
-Which one is she?-That's Brad's widow.
-她为什么这么伤心？-她发现她不是遗产受益人
-Why is she so upset?-She was cut out of the will.
难道她不知道你不能用金钱来衡量一切吗
Doesn't she know you can't define yourself by money?.
这涉及到价值、道义和你接受与给予爱的能力
It's about values and morals and your ability to give and receive love.
不知道
No.
德瑞克 抱歉，安柏
-Oh,Drake. -I'm sorry,Amber.
布莱就是这样子说的遗言
It's like Brad to have to have the last word.
抱歉，我迟到了，怎么样？
Sorry I'm late. What happened?
我们在看结局
We wanna see the end.
我要你，德瑞克
I want you,Drake.
这个我知道
I know you do.
但我们永远不可能会有结果的
But we can never be together that way.
什么？
What?
有件事我一直没有告诉你
There's something I never told you.
我是你的同父异母哥哥
I'm actually your half-brother.
那后来怎么样呢？
So what happens next?
我帮连体婴动分割手术 得了医学奖
I get the medical award for separating the Siamese twins.
然后我跟安柏去委内瑞拉 找另外一个同父异母哥哥雷蒙…
Then Amber and I go to Venezuela to meet our other half-brother,Ramon...
…我找到了世界最大的翡翠 那真的很大
...where I find the world's biggest emerald. It's really big.
但受了诅咒
But it's cursed.
好酷喔
So cool!
天啊，真是个好节目
God,that is good TV!
六人行 第2季 第18集 雷莫瑞医生之死
The One Where Dr. Ramoray Dies
菲比，跟我玩嘛
Pheebs,play with me!
不，这种游戏太畸型了
This game is grotesque!
居然把二十个手无寸铁的男人 串成一长条…
Twenty armless guys joined at the waist by a steel bar...
…被迫无止境地踢足球
...forced to play soccer forever?
简直是侵害人权嘛
Hello? Human rights violation!
不要为他们难过 等他们踢完足球之后…
Don't feel so bad. After playing...
…我把塑料小姐拿出来 大家都会非常开心的呀
...I break out the plastic women and everybody has a good time.
你干嘛不跟你室友玩？
Why don't you play with your roommate?
他不爱玩桌上足球
He's not a big fan of foosball.
你跟那个新来的处得不好吗？
Are we not getting along with the new boy?
不是啊，他很好，只是 多数的时间都关在房间里
No,he's all right. He spends most of his time in his room.
我想那也许是因为 你没有花时间去了解他
That's because you haven't gotten to know him.
我们来补救，好不好？
Let's remedy that,shall we?
我们不需要补救 要啊，会很好玩的
-We don't need to. -lt'll be fun!
什么事？
What was that?
我只是想我们三人来喝点啤酒 彼此了解一下会很有意思
I thought it'd be fun if we had beers and got to know each other.
好呀，听起来不错
All right.
好的
Oh,good! Okay.
不行，我得走了 因为我还要赶去…
Oh,no! I have to go,because I'm late for...
…“绿蛋与火腿”的研讨会（瑟斯博土最畅销的儿童小说）
... my Green Eggs and Ham discussion group.
今天晚上主题是… “为什么不在火车上吃呢？”
Tonight,it's "Why he would not eat them on a train."
好好玩，拜 好烂的借口
-Have fun! Bye! -That was so lame.
我知道
I know.
你跟他谈
Okay,talk to him.
你想那个赛车手 被开了多少罚单啊…？
So you think that Speed Racer guy gets a lot of tickets or...?
好笑…谁甩了谁啊？
That's good. So who broke up with who?
我甩了她呀
I broke up with her.
她真的以为肖恩潘（影星）是柬埔寨的首都（金边）
She actually thought Sean Penn was the capital of Cambodia.
有没有搞错？ 大家都知道柬埔寨的首都是…
When everybody knows that the capital of Cambodia is....
不是肖恩潘
It's not Sean Penn.
好，我有个好笑的
I got a funny one.
好，我前任的女友叫提莉 我们在吃早餐
My last girlfriend,Tilly. We're eating breakfast,right?
我做了很多薄松饼 大概有五十多个吧
I made these pancakes. Like,50 pancakes.
突然间她转过来 她就说艾迪…
All of a sudden,she turns to me and says,"Eddie...
…我不想再跟你见面了
... I don't wanna see you anymore."
那就好像是 她把手伸进我的胸膛里…
It was literally like she had reached into my chest...
…挖出了我的心 把我的生活搞得乱七八糟的
... ripped out my heart and smeared it all over my life!
那就像我面前有一个深渊 我就一直往下掉
There was this incredible abyss and I'm falling.
我就一直往下掉 永无止境地往下掉
I keep falling and I don't think I'm ever gonna stop!
这个故事不太好笑，是不是？
That wasn't such a funny story.
中央公园
一个坏脾气老头说我尽量
And a crusty old man Said I'll do what I can
其他老鼠开始摇响葫芦
And the rest of the rats Played maracas
唱完了，谢谢，晚安
That's it! Thanks! Good night.
菲比还有别的工作吧？
Phoebe's got another job,right?
唱得很好，菲比
Great set tonight,Pheebs.
我知道
I know.
我想我们该走了
We should get going.
我们也该走了 明天早上八点还有病人
We should too. I've got patients at 8 in the morning.
知道吗？我在想 我们老是在你那边过夜
You know how we always stay at your apartment?
或许今晚改住我那边啊
I thought tonight we'd stay at my place.
我不知道，我没有带我的睡衣
I don't know. I don't have my jammies.
或许你不需要
You don't need them.
我的小妹妹，各位先生女士
My baby sister,ladies and gentlemen.
闭嘴，我很快乐
Shut up. I'm happy.
这太棒了 我必须说几句话
Oh,this is so nice! I have to make a speech.
我只是想说，在莫妮卡 交过的为数众多的男友当中…
Of all the guys that Monica has been with,and that is a lot...
…我最喜欢你了
...I like you the best.
谢谢你，菲比，嘴真甜
Thank you,Pheebs. That's very sweet.
听到了吗？
You hear that?
她最喜欢我 而且你显然有过很多
She likes me best. And apparently,there have been a lot.
没有啦
Not a lot.
菲比在说笑吧，菲比是疯子
Phoebe's kidding. Phoebe's crazy.
菲比死定了
Phoebe's dead.
我找艾迪
I'm looking for Eddie Manoick.
他现在不在 我叫钱德
He's not here right now. I'm Chandler.
要我帮你留话 还是…拿鱼缸呢？
Can I take a message or.... Or a fish tank?
谢了
Thanks.
请进
Come on in.
我叫提莉
I'm Tilly.
看你这个样子 他一定跟你提过我了
I gather by that "Oh," he told you about me.
提过，你的名字在一段…
Yeah,your name came up...
…令我惊心动魄的对话中 曾经出现过了
...in a conversation that terrified me to my very soul.
他这人有点激烈吧
He's kind of intense.
对呀，请问你 艾迪是不是有一点…
Yes! Hey,can I ask you,is Eddie a little...
有一点怎么样？
A little what?
…有点乡村风格？
...bit country?
或者，摇滚风格？
Or, you know, a little rock ' n' roll?
快进来呀，室友
Come on in,you roomie!
提莉
Hello,Tilly.
艾迪，我只是把鱼缸送过来
Eddie,I just came by to drop off your tank.
你想得真是周到
That was very thoughtful of you.
非常体帖
It's very thoughtful.
就这样了
Well,okay then.
我要走了，再见
I'm gonna go. Bye.
那么我们养鱼了，是不是？
So we getting a fish?
你们上床了，是不是？
You had sex with her.
菲比，你看…
Check it out,check it out!
“肥皂剧文摘” 我最喜欢的文摘之一
Soap Opera Digest! That's one of my favorite digests!
42页…
Page 42! Page 42!
医界新秀 “我们的日子”乔伊崔比亚尼
"New Doc on the Block,Days of our Lives Joey Tribbiani."
好酷的照片
Cool picture!
我好帅
Oh,I look good.
这是真的吗？ 很多台词都是你自己写的吗？
Is this true? That you write a lot of your own lines?
可以这么说啦
Well,kind of,yeah.
比如你记得上礼拜 阿莱克斯出了事那一集吗？
Remember last week when Alex was in the accident?
剧本上的台词是…
The line in the script was...
…“我们不送这女人去医院的话，她会死的”
... "If we don't get this woman to a hospital,she's going to die."
被我改成了这个女人不去医院就医的话…
But I made it,"If this woman doesn't get to a hospital...
…她会活不成的
...she's not gonna live."
我懂你做了什么了
Oh,okay. I see what you did there.
那你不怕那些编剧 看到这篇文章会有点生气吗？
Aren't you afraid the writers will be kind of mad when they read this?
我倒没有考虑到那些编剧 剧本总是送来我家
I never thought about the writers. The scripts just come to my house.
但你知道吗？
But you know what?
这样让我很有面子 也因为这样子，节目有面子…
This makes me look good,which makes the show look good...
…也因为这样子，编剧有面子 他们怎么可能会生我的气呢？
...which makes the writers look good. So how could they be mad?
“我们的日子”
他编了自己大部份的台词
Makes up most of his lines.
很好…
Son of a....
写这个，混蛋
Write this,jerk-weed.
我跌下了电梯井
I fall down an elevator shaft?
这什么意思？我跌下了电梯井
What does this mean? I fall down an elevator shaft?
我不知道，我只是送剧本过来
I don't know. I just bring the scripts.
他们不能杀我 我是弗兰西斯卡失散的儿子呀
They can't kill me! I'm Francesca's long-lost son!
对
Right.
请你签收，好吗？
Could you sign?
我才不签呢
No! No way! I'm not signing that!
我不认为 对那个节目的剧情会有影响啊
I don't think that will affect the plot of the show.
他们怎么能这么对我？
How can they do this to me?
我要走了
All right,I'm just gonna go.
很遗憾
Sorry.
也没有那么多个啦
Well,it wasn't that many guys.
我是说，如果你考虑到 全世界有多少男人…
If you consider how many guys there actually are...
…那个比例非常小
...it's a very small percentage.
没什么大不了的 我只是…好奇罢了
It's not that big a deal. I was just curious.
晚安 晚安，理查
-Good night. -Good night,Richard.
祝你好运，莫妮卡
Good luck,Mon.
好，在我说之前 你先说你有过几个女人
Before I tell you,you tell me how many women you've been with.
两个
Two.
两个？…
Two? Two?
那怎么可能？…
How is that possible? I mean...
…你知道你长得有多帅吗？
... have you seen you?
我能说什么呢？
I mean,what can I say?
我跟芭芭拉做了三十年的夫妻 我们在高中就认识了
I was married to Barbara for 30 years,my high-school sweetheart.
加上你，一共两个
Now you. That's two.
那就两个吧
Two it is.
该上床了 我要去刷牙了
Time for bed. I'm gonna brush my teeth.
你先等一等
No,wait a minute now!
来啊，换你了
Come on,it's your turn.
快说呀
Oh,come on!
我不需要确切数字 只要约略估计的（有“棒球场”的含义）就可以了
You know,I don't need the actual number. Just a ballpark.
绝对比一个“棒球场”少
Okay,it is definitely less than a ballpark.
真庆幸现在我不是莫妮卡
I am so glad I'm not Monica right now.
那还用说
Tell me about it.
你的神奇数字是多少？
So what's your magic number?
来嘛，我交过的你都认识 两个你都认识
Come on,you know everyone I've been with. All both of them.
有你
Well,there's you.
最好不要排名
Better not be doing these in order.
比利,皮特
Billy Dreskin,Pete Carny.
贝瑞
Barry.
还有…保罗
Paolo.
对，托里尼来的蠢蛋
Oh,yes,the weenie from Turinie.
亲爱的，你嫉妒保罗吗？
Honey,are you jealous of Paolo?
跟他从没像跟你在一起 这么快乐过
I'm so much happier with you than I ever was with him.
真的？ 拜托
-Really? -Oh,please!
跟保罗那一段根本就不能算
That Paolo thing was barely a relationship.
那只能算是 无意义的野兽的性关系
All it really was was just meaningless,animal sex.
我这么说让我自己觉得好多了
Okay,you know,that sounded so much better in my head.
艾迪 我没有跟你的前任女友上床
I didn't sleep with your ex-girlfriend.
有意思，因为跟她上过床的人 都会这么说
That's exactly what someone who slept with her would say.
你疯了，你疯了，是不是？ 她只来了两分钟而已…
This is nuts! Crazy! She came over for two minutes...
…丢下鱼缸就走了就是这样
...dropped off a fish tank and left!
巴迪在哪里？
Where's Buddy?
巴迪？
Buddy?
我的鱼巴迪
My fish,Buddy.
她根本就没有带鱼来 里面没有任何东西
There was no fish when she dropped it off.
这真令人难以置信
This is unbelievable!
你先跟我的前任女友上床 以为我会笨到去相信你的谎言
You sleep with my ex-girlfriend,insult my intelligence by lying...
然后你杀了我的鱼 我的巴迪？
...then you kill my fish? My Buddy?
我没有杀你的鱼啊
I didn't kill your fish!
你听我说，艾迪…
Look,Eddie
你看我在做什么啊
Would you look at what I'm doing?
那样太不聪明了
Now that can't be smart.
所以我们要把那个家伙 给拿开…
So we're just gonna take this guy right off you...
…把它放到我的口袋先生里
...and put him here in Mr. Pocket.
来个橘子吧
Tangelo?
就这样吗？ 这就是你害怕告诉我的庞大数目吗？
That's it? That's the giant number you were afraid to tell me?
那还好嘛
Well,that's not bad at all.
我是说，你害我以为 你有一舰队的人
You had me thinking it was,like,a fleet.
你真的觉得没关系？
You're okay with it?
亲爱的，没关系
Oh,honey,I'm fine.
对了，关于那两个…
Okay,about that two.
什么？
What?
好吧
All right.
我的“两个”怎么了？
What about my two?
只是听起来真的好少喔
It just seems like a really small number.
对呀
Right.
我是说，难道你没有许多的燕麦去播种吗？
Don't you have a lot of wild oats to sow?
你现在就是在那样对我吗？ 天啊，我是燕麦吗？
Or is that what you're doing with me? Oh,my God! Am I an oat?
亲爱的，你不是燕麦
Honey,you are not an oat.
我不知道 我猜我不是那一型的
I don't know,I guess I'm just not an oat guy.
我只跟我爱的女人上床
I've only slept with women I love.
但是你只跟两个人上过床
You've only slept with two people.
对
Right.
你一定知道我也爱你吧？
You know I love you too,right?
现在我知道了
Now I do.
罗斯…拜托听我说
Ross,please listen to me.
罗斯，你比保罗好太多了
You are so much better for me than Paolo ever was.
我是说，你关心我 你心中有爱，你会逗我笑
You care about me,you're loving,you make me laugh.
那样的话，我有个主意
If I make you laugh,here's an idea.
你可以邀请保罗过来 在床上野兽一下…
Invite Paolo to have a romp in the sack...
…而我就站在角落 讲敲门的笑话
...and I'll stand in the corner and tell knock-knock jokes!
罗斯，我们的感情很特别！ 我跟保罗有的只是…
What we have is special! All Paolo and I ever had was
“野兽的性关系”？
"Animal sex"?
所以你什么意思呢？
So what are you saying?
你是说我们之间 就没有任何“兽性”的东西吗
There's nothing between us "animal" at all?
连一点点…一点兽性都没有？
There's not even,like,a little animal?
甚至都不像…
Not even,like...
…花栗鼠那样的性？
...chipmunk sex?
拜托，你听我说
Try to hear me,okay?
我不想对你说谎
I'm not gonna lie to you.
跟保罗的性很好 敲敲门
-lt was good with Paolo. -Knock-knock.
但我们两个之间的比那好多了
But what you and I have is so much better.
我们有温柔，我们有亲密 我们心灵相通
We have tenderness,we have intimacy,we connect.
而且我发誓
You know? I swear.
我从来没有过…
This is the best...
…像你这么棒的
... I have ever had.
直到现在
Until now.
理查刚说他爱我
Richard told me he loved me.
天啊 我知道
-Oh,my God! -I know!
太棒了
Honey,that's great!
我知道
I know!
我只是找不到… 在第一个抽屉
-I just can't find -Top drawer.
你也要啊 对呀
-Hurry. -Why? You need one too?
找到了
Found them!
只有一个
There's only one.
我马上来 我们…在决定事情
We'll be right there. We're just trying to decide something.
她们两个在决定事情 好，很好
-They're trying to decide something. -Good. Good,good.
你的…你的小胡子 跟以前有不同吗？
So was your mustache Did it used to be different?
你怎么能够保持得那么整齐？
How do you,you know,keep it so neat?
我有一把小梳子
I have a comb.
那个梳子叫什么？ 胡子梳
-What is that? -A mustache comb.
谢谢
Thank you.
我帮你洗一个月的衣服
Okay,I will do your laundry for one month.
我会…我会…
I will,I will,I will....
我打扫两个月的房子，如何？
I will clean the apartment for two months.
只要你告诉我我们把簸箕 放在哪里，这个我现在给你
I'll give this to you now,if you tell me where we keep the dustpan.
你有没有打过越战？
So were you in Nam?
我们都是成年人了对吧？所以应该用成年人的方式处理
We are both adults here. Right?. There has to be a mature way to handle this.
剪刀石头布 没问题
-Rock,paper,scissors? -Gotcha.
一，二，三
One,two,three.
太棒了
Yes!
很好，上床吧
Fine. Go have sex.
不对，你完完全全搞错了
No! You have got it completely wrong!
约翰萨维奇是《猎鹿人》里没有腿的那个
John Savage was Deer Hunter,no legs.
约翰沃特是《归乡》里腿瘫痪的那个（都是越战电影）
Jon Voight was Coming Home,couldn't feel his legs.
你完完全全搞反了（理查是正确的），朋友，约翰沃特是…
You've got it totally the other way around,my friend. Jon Voight
亲爱的 什么？
-Honey? -What?
可以了吗
Shall we?
今晚不可能了
It's not gonna happen.
今天晚上他们做 我们可以明天再做
They're doing it tonight. We can do it tomorrow.
下一次的时间表 可不可以先让我看看？
In the future,if I could see the schedule beforehand....
我今天早上醒过来的时候…
So when I woke up this morning...
…发现他偷了我所有的鞋垫
... he'd stolen all the insoles out of my shoes!
为什么？
Why?
那家伙以为我睡了他前任女友 而且还杀了他的鱼
He thinks I slept with his ex-girlfriend and killed his fish.
你干嘛杀了他的鱼？
Why would you kill his fish?
菲比，因为有时候 你跟人上床之后…
Because sometimes after you sleep with someone...
…就必须要杀条鱼
...you have to kill a fish.
钱德，宝贝…
Chandler,honey...
…很遗憾
... I'm sorry.
可以看乔伊的电视剧了吗？
Can we watch Joey's show now,please?
等等，他还没有到
Wait. He's not here yet.
他知道情节
He knows what happens.
顺便说一句，我不在乎我的问题了
I'm fine about my problem now,by the way.
安柏…
Amber...
…你需要的时候永远有我…
...I'll always be there for you...
…我是你一辈子的朋友跟兄弟
...as a friend and as your brother.
德瑞克
Oh,Drake.
辛苦了
Hard day,huh?
先是医学大奖，然后是这个
First the medical award,now this?
是呀，我猜有些人天生好运
Some guys are just lucky,I guess.
雷莫瑞大夫，请到一楼急诊室
Dr. Ramoray,report to first floor Emergency stat.
那么…
Well,then...
…我猜在叫我了
... I guess that's me.
还有谁想坐电梯的？郝顿大夫？华大夫？
Anyone else need to go on the elevator? Dr. Horton? Dr. Wall?
他们只叫你一个人啊
They only said you.
好吧
Oh,okay. All right.
我爱你，德瑞克
I love you.
是呀，随便啦
Yeah,whatever.
不…
Oh,no!
德瑞克，小心，德瑞克…
Drake,look out!
他们刚刚杀了乔伊？ 不可能
-Did they just kill off Joey? -No!
好像真的
Now maybe.
开门，我们想跟你谈一谈
Come on! Open up! We want to talk to you!
我不想谈
I don't feel like talking!
别这样了，乔伊 我们关心你
Come on! We care about you.
我们很关心你 我们有些人真的很急要尿尿
-We're worried about you. -And some of us really have to pee!
很遗憾，乔伊
I'm sorry,Joey.
听着，很遗憾你的死 真的很惨耶
Listen,sorry about your death. That really sucks.
我们一看到就赶过来了 你怎么不告诉我们呢？
-We came over as soon as we saw. -How could you not tell us?
我不知道 我有点希望没有人会发现
I don't know. I was kind of hoping no one would ever find out.
或许他们可以让你起死回生
Well,maybe they could find a way to bring you back.
他们说当找到我尸体的时候 我的脑袋已经摔得稀巴烂了…
They said that when they found my body,my brain was so smashed in...
…而唯一救得了我的人是我
...that the only doctor who could've saved me was me.
说是故意要看起来讽刺什么的
It's supposed to be some kind of irony.
乔伊，你不会有事的
But Joey,you're gonna be fine.
你不需要那个节目 那只是个蠢的肥皂剧嘛
You don't need that show. It was just a dumb soap opera.
菲比，那是我这辈子最棒的事
This was the greatest thing that ever happened to me.
没错，我本来还要那样说的
Yes! I was going to incorporate that.
很好，莫妮卡来了 她会说句好听的啦
Here's Monica. She'll have something nice to say.
我把你的浴帘拉直了以免发霉
I straightened out your shower curtain so you won't get mildew.
怎么了？对我来说那是好事啊
What? To me,that's nice.
不要紧的，你也知道嘛
It'll be okay. You know that.
不，我不知道
No,I don't.
像你奋斗了一辈子去追求…
It's like you work your whole life for something...
…当你认为你办到的时候…
...and you think that when you get it...
…永远不会像你想的一样好
...it'll never be as good as you thought.
不过这个是啊
But this so was.
它改变了一切
It changed everything.
前几天呢，我去申请信用卡…
Like,the other day,I got this credit card application...
…我竟然被预先审核了
...and I was pre-approved!
我这辈子从没被预先审核过
I've never been pre-approved for anything in my life!
很遗憾，老兄
I'm sorry,man.
乔伊 我不知道这对你有没有意义…
I don't know if this'll mean anything to you...
…但我们总是会审核你过关的
... but you'll always be pre-approved with us.
不，那对我没有意义
That means nothing to me.
大胡桃饼，刚出炉的
Pecan sandy? Just made them.
好
Yeah,all right.
这是葡萄干吗？
Are these raisins?
当然了，有何不可？
Sure,why not?
听我说，艾迪
Listen,Eddie.
我想过 我们目前住在一起的情况了
I've been thinking about our living situation.
你为什么要笑？
Why are you smiling?
我有个小小的惊喜 我买了条新鱼
I got a little surprise. Look. There's a new fishy.
我叫它…
I named him...
…钱德，以你为名
... Chandler,you know,after you.
那根本不是一条真鱼啊
Well,that's not even a real fish.
那是金鱼饼干耶
No,that's a Goldfish cracker.
你要说什么？
So what's your point,man?
晚安了
Okay,good night.
你这个自然的大怪人
You big freak of nature!
今天晚上好冷 老兄
-Brisk tonight. -Oh,man.
我们都不要提了 没问题
-Let's never speak of this. -You got it.